rvusa.com 2011-11-22

# RVUSA.com Privacy Policy

    * Sell My RV
  * RV Marketplace
    * Search RVs For Sale
    * Browse RVs for Sale
    * RV Dealers
    * RV Manufacturers
    * RVs For Rent
    * RV Parts & Accessories
    * RV Product Manufacturers
    * RV Service
    * RV Storage
    * RV Road Service
    * RV Financing
    * RV Insurance
    * RV Extended Warranties
  * RV Guide & Lifestyle
    * RV Forums
    * RV Parks & Campgrounds
    * Newcomer’s RV Guide
    * RV Shows & Events
    * RV Clubs
    * RV Magazines
    * Tourism and Travel Links
    * Outdoor Cooking Recipes
  * About RVUSA
    * Testimonials
    * Advertise with RVUSA
    * Privacy Policy
    * Contact Us
    * Site Map

### UPCOMING RV SHOWS

1/5/2012 - 1/8/2012 San Antonio, Texas – THE SOUTH TEXAS RV SUPERSALE Exposition Hall at Joe Freeman Coliseum  
3201 East Houston Street   
San Antonio, Texas 78219 

1/6/2012 - 1/8/2012 23rd Annual North Carolina RV & Camping Show Greensboro Coliseum - Greensboro, NC

1/6/2012 - 1/8/2012 2nd Annual New Mexico RV, Boat & Travel Show Albuquerque Convention Center - Albuquerque, NM

1/11/2012 - 1/14/2012 22nd Annual Colorado RV Adventure Travel Show Colorado Convention Center - Denver, CO

1/13/2012 - 1/15/2012 26th Annual Washington Camping RV Expo Dulles Expo Center - Chantilly, VA

1/20/2012 - 1/22/2012 16th Annual North Carolina's RV Show Raleigh Convention Center - Raleigh, NC

1/20/2012 - 1/22/2012 45th Annual New Jersey RV & Camping Show New Jersey Convention Center - Edison, NJ

1/26/2012 - 1/29/2012 Mid-America RV Show Kansas City Convention Center - Kansas City, MO

1/27/2012 - 1/29/2012 Atlanta Camping & RV Show Atlanta Exposition CenterSouth  
(Interstate 285 to Jonesboro Road, Exit 55)

2/9/2012 - 2/12/2012 45th Annual Minneapolis St. Paul RV, Vacation & Camping Show Minneapolis Convention Center - Minneapolis, MN

  * [RVUSA.com](http://www.rvusa.com/ "Home - RVUSA.com") »
  * Privacy Policy

  * What information do you collect?
  * How do you collect information?
  * How information will be used?
  * User choices in receiving and distribution of information
  * Data Security
  * Data Quality & Access
  * Questions

### What information do you collect?

**Personal Information:**  
We require personal contact information and vehicle information from our customers. The required information is used to effectively and accurately create, maintain, and display RVUSA.com’s RV vehicle for sale database, and to track and verify users in our forums. The required vehicle information we collect is only that which is necessary to accurately search and display your vehicle in our database. Information collected to access our forums is used to validate users and the display of any personal information such as e-mail address is optional based on the users choice.

**Cookies:**  
Currently, the RVUSA.com website does not use cookies to track visitor activities on our website. Any changes to that policy will be reflected by a change in our Privacy Policy.

### How do you collect information?

Members are requested to submit personal and vehicle information using the forums and RV Listing services. Credit Card and billing information will only be collected for services that RVUSA.com charges a fee for. Users unwilling to pass personal information online for our paid services can choose to work with a customer service representative via phone. All free services require the use of our online registration.

### How information will be used?

**Resale and Disclosure of Information**  
RVUSA.com is a division of NetSource Media. RVUSA.com and NetSource Technologies, Inc do not sell, share or disclose any information collected from our visitors with any outside parties other than the transmission of credit card billing information with our credit card processing company.

**Privacy of RVUSA.com Email Lists**  
We collect and record personal information in order to maintain email lists. We utilize the emails to keep members informed of the site services, site performance, promotions, and offer information regarding industry related services and products.

### User choices in receiving and distribution of information

**RVUSA.com Email Lists**  
Dealer members receive periodic emails informing them of special promotions and advertising tips. Dealers who wish not to receive these emails can send a request via email to be removed from the mailing list. Private party members automatically receive an email to confirm their placement on our site and to give them the necessary information to edit and delete their classified ad. Private parties also receive notification of ad renewal opportunities 15, 10, and 5 days before expiration. RVUSA.com reserves the right to include third party advertisements that provide additional services to members in the confirmation emails.

### Data Security

**Personal Information**  
To protect the member's account information, RVUSA.com assigns each member with either a unique user name or password or a unique ad ID number. These unique identifiers are disclosed to the user via email immediately upon joining the RVUSA.com forums or listing a vehicle for sale. Only members have the ability to modify their personal information and delete their ads as needed.

**Credit Card Transactions**  
RVUSA.com uses Verisign Certification and secure servers to transmit all online credit card transactions in an encrypted format.

### Data Quality and Access

Members may access their information 24 hours a day using their designated user name and password or ad ID number. Members may modify or delete their information as needed.

### Questions

If you have further questions that were not addressed in the above **Privacy Policy** , please call RVUSA at **(866) 643-4625**  
or fill out our contact form.
